Wow great! Thank you so much!
Cute!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What? What? What?
You're making me hungry. Please.
Yes, sir.
preview of next part
Part 2
Next preview
What a me banser!
I won 3 million yen in the quiz!
I won 3 million yen!
It's the best!
Um, is this the 7th time for Hinatazaka?
How is that possible?
But I wanted to tell everyone how I felt about the 3 million yen,
Oh, really?
I also have 2 million, which I hope to use for a tour or something.
I can't get Sora-chan!
What?
Three million?
Hey, I'm going for it.
Boom!
Yes, time has passed since then. Yes, time has passed since then.
After much consultation with the staff
After much discussion with the staff, it was decided that
Grape Shop will be coming to the 2nd day performance in Aichi!
Yay!
We are going without any public announcement to the members
Don't tell the members.
We hope to be able to serve them on the second day of the show in Aichi!
The menu is not very original.
I have some ideas for the menu that I would like to propose.
But what would you like?
I think there are many members who like strawberries.
I think there are a lot of members who like strawberries, so maybe I can put strawberries in it. I don't know.
There is a grape wrapping paper, like a wrapping paper.
I drew a rough sketch, or rather
I drew a rough sketch, or rather a simple sketch, and I was asked to design it based on it.
I'd like to write it down.
If it's a kitchen car, could it be something like this?
I'd like to make it a kitchen car with a little bit of a Japanese style.
See you in the next video!
This... this cafe?
This is fun.
I'm not only a broadcaster.
I'd like to be involved in the menu.
Adding strawberries...
Crepes with octopus and mushrooms.
Can't you just do that?
Can't you just pop it on top?
What's that?
Mushrooms?Mushrooms?
I don't know.
Like cookies.
Like octopus cookies.
Like cookies with an illustration of an octopus on them.
I don't know if you can do that.
I just made a great discovery.
Mark, this is the official bear footprint crepe.
But if you flip it over like this...
Oh my!
I thought it was an octopus.
with a chocolate pen or something...
What do you think?
That's nice.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
Like this.
I'm sure it will become a reality from here.
Please look forward to it!
Here we are!
It's the second day at Aichi Park!
Yay!
Today is the day to finally unveil it to everyone!
So, it's already right over here, so I'll show it to you!
Seino!
Cheers!
Whoo!
It's Mr. Bear's Asiatocrepe!
Yay!
That's great! Already.
A lot of them around here. Lots of them around here.
Look, a rice cafe.
I designed this one, too.
I think I also came up with the collaboration menu.
Can you show us the menu and the broadcast paper as well?
Yes!
I'm looking forward to it! I haven't actually seen anything yet.
I'm going to take a look now for the first time.
Oh!
Is it on?
Here it comes! Wow! It's so cute! Thank you!
It's so cute! Look! Look!
It's a chocolate from Bear Footprints Quest, isn't it?
We were talking about turning the chocolate upside down to make an octopus.
Here it is! Look! He's peeking out!
Can I try some of these?
Yes! Go ahead!
Are you sure you don't mind?
Yes!
Strawberries!
I was very particular and insisted on strawberries.
Bon appétit!
Yum! Ah!
The frozen strawberries are so delicious and crunchy!
Thank goodness for strawberries!
Turn this over.
I'll show you guys the pine taco.
Here we go!
Here, here, here, here...
Oh, no!Oh no!
You made me laugh.
So this is how the octopus appears.
So cute! Look at this.
Thank you for the octopus next to this kamatsuga!
By the way, is it OK if I use the name of the menu that I came up with?
Yes! By all means!
Can we call it "Konoka Special"?
KONOKA SPECIAL
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'm going to go with "This one special".
Yes, please.
Oh, my gosh!
I can't wait to see your reactions.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes! It's done!
I'd like to make a spot where it's easy for the members to take pictures.
I'm hoping to create a spot where the members can take pictures.
Like this?
I think it would be nice if we could take pictures of the crepes and the members all the time.
That's great!
It's 2:26 p.m. right now.
The cafe car is supposed to start at 2:30 p.m.
3 more minutes! The members will be here in 3 minutes!
Fidgety!
I hope they're happy.
I hope they're happy?
This café sticker. This cafesticker.
What's it called?
It's for you.
I don't know.
Do you think I should put it on? Right now.
All of you?
Here you go, sir.
There you go.
That's right.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
What is this?
Wow!
This café
You can make this?
What?
I don't know.
I've got an idea.
That's it, isn't it?
Wow.
I'll use the winnings from the Shanghainese quiz to pay for it.
I got him to come this time.
Yay!
I'm so sorry.
We have a menu that we invented.
It's so good!
Give him a sticker, too.And give him a sticker.
Please take it.
Thank you very much.
Oh!
Gummies from the quiz on commercial words.
Thank you very much.
Please eat them.
I'd love some.
Ask, ask, ask.
Whatever you want.
Don't worry about it.
Matsuda-kun chocolate.
I really want some.
I'm so happy.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
By all means!
Oh, here it is!
Bon appétit!
Ta-da!
I'll have the Matsuda-san special, too.
Matsuda-san special, please.
One, please.
How is it?
Good? It's good.
I'll have one.
It's cute.
Oh! Nice bite.
Good? It's good.Is it good? Good.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
The color of a happy woman.
Yes, it is. Thank you. For noticing.
Delicious. Thank you.
Excuse me. This is...
What is this?
These are banana oreos.
They're also delicious.
Delicious.
Octopus and Octopus.
Octopus and water octopus!
I'm so happy. I eat a lot. Kanamura...
Yes, I'll eat all of them. All of them.
Mari is amazing. Mari Mari.
Thank you.
I'll take it.
I got it.
It's an octopus from this cafe.
Special and
Caramel Cafe.
Caramel Cafe Banana!
Bon appétit!
I'll have the food for the special later.
I'll have this cup special, please.
You said this cup special.
Thank you very much.
He's so cute.
I'm so happy. I'm so happy.
I'm kind of pissed off.
That's a mouth full of yankees.
So cute, everyone is so happy to eat so innocently
It's too peaceful.
Thank you very much.
Thank you
Colonga special, please.
Today.
Aichus.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
May I have a chocolate banana?
A chocolate banana?
I thought it was the pineapple special.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Chocolate?
It's not a good seller.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Then I'll give you this.
Matsuda Konoka, this is Takahiro.
It has been a rumor among all the staff
that Konoka Matsuda has opened a kitchen car.
Everyone was very happy.
So I will order the Konoka Special too. So I will ask for the Konoka Special too.
Thanks Matsuda.
I will try it. Bon appétit.
Mmm! But it's delicious!
This is delicious! Surely, this is the place!
It says "this cafe" on it, and there are many places.
Matsuda's box is here!
This is Matsuda Lake.
It's a box, but I think it's an octopus dumpling shop.
And the fact that it's a crepe shop...
Matsuda's imagination is boundless.
Delicious!
I love this guy.
Wow! Thank you!
This is my first time. I know it's tonight, but thank you so much, this one.
No, no, no, please eat it.
Looks delicious.
Cute. Octopus.
Mamy bread.
Look, look, look.
I wonder what this cafe is called.
That's right.
I came to this cafe.
Ah, you too, Meimei.
Meimei.
This cafe.
Meimei-san.
What would you like?
What do you recommend? What do you recommend?
I would recommend
I'd recommend the konoka special.
But you can have whatever you want.
I'll have the konoka special.
I'm so happy!
Bon appétit!
Here you go!
Thank you!
So, Nagoya 2nd day is over.
Haruharu!
Are you coming? Are you okay?
Haruharu is watching over us!
So, we've successfully brought in the food.
All the members had big smiles on their faces.
"Thanks to the crepes, I was able to do my best.
I was able to do my best because of the crepes..." and "I was able to work hard because of the crepes.
There were so many kind members and the staff was so happy to see us.
The staff was also very happy.
I hope I was able to contribute to everyone's happiness, even if only a little.
It was a very happy day for me!
I will do my best for the upcoming tours!
Thank you very much!
This cafe!
The end!